bistri.com 2013-05-20

# None

  * What this Privacy Policy covers
  * Information that Bistri collects
  * What is public and what is private?
  * Bistri's communication platforms
  * Bistri's use of cookies
  * Information usage and sharing
  * Editing and deleting your account information
  * Feedback and Support

Last updated: May 10, 2011 

#### What this Privacy Policy covers

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the websites and services offered by Bistri. By visiting or using Bistri, you agree to this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any websites, products or services that are not owned or operated by Bistri or to actions taken by Bistri users. For example, this Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party applications that are available through Bistri, or to any social networks or IM service providers that you associate with your Bistri account, all of which are governed by their own privacy policies.

#### Information that Bistri collects

_Personally identifiable information_

Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to determine your personal identity, such as your name or email address. When you create an account we ask for your name and email address. If you link your third-party instant messaging (IM) accounts to your Bistri account, we may also collect your user name for that account, which is also considered personally identifiable information.

_Optional profile data_

Bistri gives you the opportunity to update your public profile with information about yourself such as your photo, your hometown, your website and a short biography. This information is public as described under "What is public and what is private?"

_Information from the accounts you link to Bistri_

If you connect your Bistri account to your third-party IM accounts or your social network accounts (e.g., Facebook and Twitter), they may send us information about you, including your name, username at those services, Unique User ID ("UUID") for those services, friends list, status, profile information, age and gender.

_Demographic data_

Bistri asks for your age and gender at registration and may collect additional demographic information about you, such as your location and interests. Bistri may receive this information from you or from outside sources, such as websites where the Bistri Bar is present, ad networks and other providers, or we may make assumptions based on the other information that we collect.

_Log data_

When you use Bistri, we automatically collect information about you and your activity known as "log data", including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser or device type, your interactions with other users. Bistri stores and uses this log data based on an anonymous identifier.

#### What is public and what is private?

_Public information_

as Bistri profiles, are public in order to allow people to find each other. This section describes which information is public. Public information is available to everyone on the Internet and can be viewed, copied, indexed, transferred and searched. 

  * _Your profile_. Your Bistri public profile and all of the information on it, including your picture, are all public.

_Private Information_

The following information is not made available as part of your public profile or otherwise made public by Bistri: 

  * your age and gender
  * your email address
  * your third-party IM account user names
  * your third-party IM account buddies or third-party (e.g., Facebook) social network friends
  * your IM communications
  * your log data

#### Bistri's communication platforms

Bistri offers users the ability to communicate with each other through IM, Voice and Video. Don't share personal information unless it's someone you know well in the real world.

When you create a Bistri account, your preferences are set to enable all Bistri users to send you an IM, but only people who you authorize can see if you are online. You can change those authorizations when you want.

Your preferences are also automatically set to store your IM history on Bistri's servers. You can view or delete your IM history by clicking on the IM history icon in your chat window. You can turn off the IM history feature in your Bistri Messenger account under "Preferences."

Keep in mind that even if you elect not to store your IM history, the person that you'recommunicating with may be storing your conversation, either on Bistri, on their IM network's servers or on their own computers. By using Bistri, you consent to the storage of your IM history on Bistri as the default option and to the storing of your IM history by other users with whom you are chatting or by the Third Party IM Service that you or your friend is using.

#### Bistri's use of cookies

Bistri uses cookies. Bistri does not store personally identifiable information or passwords in its cookies.

We use these cookies to provide you with a better Bistri experience, such as by recognizing you when you come to Bistri, by remembering if you are already signed-in and by remembering information about you, like your preferences. We also use cookies to generate aggregate and anonymous data so that we can better understand and analyze how users use Bistri.

#### Information usage and sharing

If we propose to use personal information for any purpose other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out.

_Usage of information._

Bistri uses the information it collects: 

  * To provide you with access to your account;
  * To provide you with the Bistri services;
  * To enhance and improve the Bistri services;
  * To recommend to you or other Bistri users potential friends or websites that may be of interest;
  * To conduct research;
  * To determine your geographic location or other demographic information about you;
  * To create reports and to analyze usage patterns; and
  * To contact you as described under "Emails and other notifications."

_Sharing of information._

Bistri may share your non-public personally identifiable information with third parties only in the following cases: 

  * We may need to share your log-in information with the third-party IM services and networks where you have an account that you have chosen to access through Bistri in order to permit you to log onto and use that service;
  * With trusted third-party service providers who help us in the operation of Bistri and who have agreed to maintain the confidentiality of the data;
  * To the third-party applications available through Bistri, as described under "Bistri Platform";
  * When we have your consent;
  * In cases of abusive behavior or suspected violations of the terms of use of Bistri or of any third-party service accessed through or in association with Bistri, we may share personal information, including IP address, with that third party in order to investigate the violation and to take appropriate action;
  * Where we have a good faith belief that it is required in order to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, to prevent fraud or imminent harm, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * In the event that Bistri is acquired by or merged with another company or transfers substantially all of its assets to another company, Bistri will transfer all of its user information and data, including information about you, to that other company.

Bistri may share your public information or any anonymous information for any of the purposes described under "Usage of information". 

#### Editing and deleting your account information

You can edit certain personal information that you have provided or request that your account be deleted by logging into your Bistri account and accessing your account settings. Information that was already publicly shared, such as your comments or pages that you shared, and messages that you previously sent will still be visible in the various places that information is displayed.

Deleting your Bistri account does not currently automatically remove your personally identifiable information from the Bistri servers. However, if you delete your account, we will use your personally identifiable information only to investigate abuse and comply with legal requests as described under "Information usage and sharing". If you would like to have your personally identifiable information deleted, please contact us as provided under "Comments and Questions".

#### Feedback and Support

If you have any comments or questions you may address them to the customer service department at Bistri, or via mail addressed to : Customer Service, Bistri SAS, 66, avenue des Champs Elysées, 75008 Paris, France.
